Correctional Association of New York; Records apap014
M.E. Grenander Department of Special Collections & Archives
- Subject Files [RESTRICTED], 1947-1988; 1970-1985; 7; 11 cubic ft.
  - 128th Annual Report of the CANY [RESTRICTED], 1972 (Box 8 (7-Subject Files [RESTRICTED]), Folder 10)
  - Origins of the Underclass [RESTRICTED], 1986 (Box 8 (7-Subject Files [RESTRICTED]), Folder 11)
  - Osborne Association [RESTRICTED], 1961-1983 (Box 8 (7-Subject Files [RESTRICTED]), Folder 12)
  - Osborne Association - Administration [RESTRICTED], 1983-1984 (Box 8 (7-Subject Files [RESTRICTED]), Folder 13)
  - Osborne Association - Architectural Plans and Contracts [RESTRICTED], 1983 (Box 8 (7-Subject Files [RESTRICTED]), Folder 14)
  - Osborne Association - Contributions [RESTRICTED], 1986 (Box 8 (7-Subject Files [RESTRICTED]), Folder 15)
  - Osborne Association - Correspondence (Special) [RESTRICTED], 1984-1986 (Box 8 (7-Subject Files [RESTRICTED]), Folder 16)
  - Osborne Association - Dependent Care Assistance Plan [RESTRICTED], 1984-1985 (Box 8 (7-Subject Files [RESTRICTED]), Folder 17)
  - Osborne Association - Dependent Care Assistance Plan [RESTRICTED], 1984-1985 (Box 8 (7-Subject Files [RESTRICTED]), Folder 18)
  - Osborne Association - Family Works Programs [RESTRICTED], 1986 (Box 8 (7-Subject Files [RESTRICTED]), Folder 19)
  - Osborne Association - Fundraising [RESTRICTED], 1982-1985 (Box 8 (7-Subject Files [RESTRICTED]), Folder 20)
  - Osborne Association - General [RESTRICTED], 1984-1987 (Box 8 (7-Subject Files [RESTRICTED]), Folder 21)
  - Osborne Association - Live Call - In Program [RESTRICTED], 1986 (Box 8 (7-Subject Files [RESTRICTED]), Folder 22)
  - Osborne Association - Mission Statements [RESTRICTED], 1985 (Box 8 (7-Subject Files [RESTRICTED]), Folder 23)
  - Osborne Association - Miscellaneous [RESTRICTED], 1982-1984 (Box 8 (7-Subject Files [RESTRICTED]), Folder 24)
  - Osborne Association - General Support [RESTRICTED], 1986-1988 (Box 8 (7-Subject Files [RESTRICTED]), Folder 25)
  - Osborne Association - Mailings [RESTRICTED], 1988 (Box 8 (7-Subject Files [RESTRICTED]), Folder 26)
  - Osborne Association - Members [RESTRICTED], 1976-1988 (Box 8 (7-Subject Files [RESTRICTED]), Folder 27)
  - Osborne Association - Membership Renewal [RESTRICTED], 1986-1987 (Box 8 (7-Subject Files [RESTRICTED]), Folder 28)
  - Osborne Association - Newsletter [RESTRICTED], 1963-1983 (Box 8 (7-Subject Files [RESTRICTED]), Folder 29)
  - Osborne Association - Program [RESTRICTED], 1983-1984 (Box 8 (7-Subject Files [RESTRICTED]), Folder 30)
  - Osborne Association - Program Director Search [RESTRICTED], 1983 (Box 8 (7-Subject Files [RESTRICTED]), Folder 31)
  - Osborne Association - Project Hometown America [RESTRICTED], 1985 (Box 8 (7-Subject Files [RESTRICTED]), Folder 32)
  - Osborne Association - Proposals and Programs [RESTRICTED], 1984-1987 (Box 8 (7-Subject Files [RESTRICTED]), Folder 33)
  - Osborne Association - Renewal Letter [RESTRICTED], 1985 (Box 8 (7-Subject Files [RESTRICTED]), Folder 34)
  - Osborne Association - Renovation [RESTRICTED], 1983-1984 (Box 8 (7-Subject Files [RESTRICTED]), Folder 35)
  - Osborne Association - Student Recognition Day [RESTRICTED], 1988 (Box 8 (7-Subject Files [RESTRICTED]), Folder 36)
  - Osborne Association - Year - End Tax-Saving Letter [RESTRICTED], 1986 (Box 8 (7-Subject Files [RESTRICTED]), Folder 37)
  - Ossining Correctional Facility [RESTRICTED], ca. 1915-1984 (Box 8 (7-Subject Files [RESTRICTED]), Folder 38)
  - Other Organizations [RESTRICTED], 1984-1986 (Box 8 (7-Subject Files [RESTRICTED]), Folder 39)
  - Parole [RESTRICTED], 1979-1986 (Box 9 (7-Subject Files [RESTRICTED]), Folder 1)
  - Parole (Outside New York) [RESTRICTED], 1972-1982 (Box 9 (7-Subject Files [RESTRICTED]), Folder 2)
  - Parole/Probation [RESTRICTED], 1984 (Box 9 (7-Subject Files [RESTRICTED]), Folder 3)
  - Parole/Probation - Correctional Intervention [RESTRICTED], 1982 (Box 9 (7-Subject Files [RESTRICTED]), Folder 4)
  - Parole - Reports [RESTRICTED], 1975-1980 (Box 9 (7-Subject Files [RESTRICTED]), Folder 5)
  - Parolees - M.A. Thesis [RESTRICTED], 1965 (Box 9 (7-Subject Files [RESTRICTED]), Folder 6)
  - Pascual, Bonifacio Ramos [RESTRICTED], 1987 (Box 9 (7-Subject Files [RESTRICTED]), Folder 7)
  - Patterson, Robert [RESTRICTED], 1974 (Box 9 (7-Subject Files [RESTRICTED]), Folder 8)
  - Pennsylvania [RESTRICTED], 1961-1975 (Box 9 (7-Subject Files [RESTRICTED]), Folder 9)
  - Plan for Court and Probation Services [RESTRICTED], 1968 (Box 9 (7-Subject Files [RESTRICTED]), Folder 10)
  - Pornography [RESTRICTED], 1969-1971 (Box 9 (7-Subject Files [RESTRICTED]), Folder 11)
  - Position Statement on Narcotics [RESTRICTED], 1964 (Box 9 (7-Subject Files [RESTRICTED]), Folder 12)
  - Press Kit [RESTRICTED], 1986 (Box 9 (7-Subject Files [RESTRICTED]), Folder 13)
  - Press Literature [RESTRICTED], 1983-1986 (Box 9 (7-Subject Files [RESTRICTED]), Folder 14)
  - Press Releases/News Clippings [RESTRICTED], 1986-1987 (Box 9 (7-Subject Files [RESTRICTED]), Folder 15)
  - "Pretrial Diversion of Youthful Adults" [RESTRICTED], 1982 (Box 9 (7-Subject Files [RESTRICTED]), Folder 16)
  - Pretrial Release and Misconduct [RESTRICTED], 1985 (Box 9 (7-Subject Files [RESTRICTED]), Folder 17)
  - Pretrial Release Programs [RESTRICTED], 1988 (Box 9 (7-Subject Files [RESTRICTED]), Folder 18)
  - Preventive Detention [RESTRICTED], 1981 (Box 9 (7-Subject Files [RESTRICTED]), Folder 19)
  - Prison Action News [RESTRICTED], 1971 (Box 9 (7-Subject Files [RESTRICTED]), Folder 20)
  - Prison, Alternatives to [RESTRICTED], 1986 (Box 9 (7-Subject Files [RESTRICTED]), Folder 21)
  - Prison, Alternatives to - Trial Judges Conference [RESTRICTED], 1978 (Box 9 (7-Subject Files [RESTRICTED]), Folder 22)
  - Prison and Jail Overcrowding in New York State [RESTRICTED], 1982 (Box 9 (7-Subject Files [RESTRICTED]), Folder 23)
  - Prison Bond Issue [RESTRICTED], 1981 (Box 9 (7-Subject Files [RESTRICTED]), Folder 24)
  - Prison Bond Campaign [RESTRICTED], 1982 (Box 9 (7-Subject Files [RESTRICTED]), Folder 25)
  - Prison Bonds/Taxes - Passed/Rejected [RESTRICTED], ca. 1980 (Box 9 (7-Subject Files [RESTRICTED]), Folder 26)
  - Prison Culture [RESTRICTED], 1966 (Box 9 (7-Subject Files [RESTRICTED]), Folder 27)
  - Prison Furloughs [RESTRICTED], 1988 (Box 9 (7-Subject Files [RESTRICTED]), Folder 28)
  - Prison Industries [RESTRICTED], 1973-1984 (Box 9 (7-Subject Files [RESTRICTED]), Folder 29)
  - Prison Industries [RESTRICTED], 1981-1984 (Box 9 (7-Subject Files [RESTRICTED]), Folder 30)
  - Prison/Jail Construction [RESTRICTED], 1983-1985 (Box 9 (7-Subject Files [RESTRICTED]), Folder 31)
  - Prison Libraries [RESTRICTED], 1971 (Box 9 (7-Subject Files [RESTRICTED]), Folder 32)
  - Prison Overcrowding [RESTRICTED], 1982-1985 (Box 9 (7-Subject Files [RESTRICTED]), Folder 33)
  - Prison Overworking Articles [RESTRICTED], 1981-1982 (Box 9 (7-Subject Files [RESTRICTED]), Folder 34)
  - Prison Population Data [RESTRICTED], 1975-1984 (Box 9 (7-Subject Files [RESTRICTED]), Folder 35)
  - Prison Population Management, Calculations for Estimated Savings from Implementation of [RESTRICTED], 1984 (Box 9 (7-Subject Files [RESTRICTED]), Folder 36)
  - Prison Population Management, Calculations for Estimated Savings from Implementation of [RESTRICTED], Undated (Box 9 (7-Subject Files [RESTRICTED]), Folder 37)
  - Prison Population Management [RESTRICTED], 1984 (Box 9 (7-Subject Files [RESTRICTED]), Folder 38)
  - Prison Population - Rates of Incarceration - Total Numbers - Racial Disparities [RESTRICTED], 1979-1987 (Box 9 (7-Subject Files [RESTRICTED]), Folder 39)
  - Prison Riots/Disturbances, News Clippings [RESTRICTED], 1983 (Box 9 (7-Subject Files [RESTRICTED]), Folder 40)
  - Prison Work - Programs [RESTRICTED], 1983-1984 (Box 9 (7-Subject Files [RESTRICTED]), Folder 41)
  - Prisoners' Aid Societies [RESTRICTED], 1970-1978 (Box 9 (7-Subject Files [RESTRICTED]), Folder 42)
  - Prisoners' Bill of Rights [RESTRICTED], Undated (Box 9 (7-Subject Files [RESTRICTED]), Folder 43)
  - Prisoners' Families [RESTRICTED], 1970-1982 (Box 9 (7-Subject Files [RESTRICTED]), Folder 44)
  - Prisoners on the Payroll [RESTRICTED], Undated (Box 9 (7-Subject Files [RESTRICTED]), Folder 45)
  - Prisons - Children [RESTRICTED], 1985-1986 (Box 9 (7-Subject Files [RESTRICTED]), Folder 46)
  - Prisons - Federal [RESTRICTED], 1985-1986 (Box 9 (7-Subject Files [RESTRICTED]), Folder 47)
  - Prisons - Other Countries [RESTRICTED], 1983-1984 (Box 9 (7-Subject Files [RESTRICTED]), Folder 48)
  - Prisons, Parole and probation - Changes over the Years [RESTRICTED], 1984 (Box 9 (7-Subject Files [RESTRICTED]), Folder 49)
  - Prisons - Private [RESTRICTED], 1984-1985 (Box 9 (7-Subject Files [RESTRICTED]), Folder 50)
  - Prisons - Private [RESTRICTED], 1984-1986 (Box 9 (7-Subject Files [RESTRICTED]), Folder 51)
  - Prisons Under the Capitalist System [RESTRICTED], 1972 (Box 9 (7-Subject Files [RESTRICTED]), Folder 52)
  - Probation [RESTRICTED], 1970-1982 (Box 9 (7-Subject Files [RESTRICTED]), Folder 53)
  - Probation [RESTRICTED], 1980-1987 (Box 9 (7-Subject Files [RESTRICTED]), Folder 54)
  - Probation [RESTRICTED], 1988 (Box 9 (7-Subject Files [RESTRICTED]), Folder 55)
  - Project on Correctional Legislation [RESTRICTED], 1972-1973 (Box 9 (7-Subject Files [RESTRICTED]), Folder 56)
  - Proposed New York Penal Law [RESTRICTED], 1964 (Box 9 (7-Subject Files [RESTRICTED]), Folder 57)
  - Prostitution [RESTRICTED], 1958-1970 (Box 9 (7-Subject Files [RESTRICTED]), Folder 58)
  - Protect Prisoners' Constitutional Rights, Report of the Goldman Panel to [RESTRICTED], 1971 (Box 9 (7-Subject Files [RESTRICTED]), Folder 59)
  - Psychological Power and Pathology of Imprisonment [RESTRICTED], 1971 (Box 9 (7-Subject Files [RESTRICTED]), Folder 60)
  - Public Affairs Report [RESTRICTED], 1971-1972 (Box 9 (7-Subject Files [RESTRICTED]), Folder 61)
  - Public Opinion Polls [RESTRICTED], 1987 (Box 9 (7-Subject Files [RESTRICTED]), Folder 62)
  - Public Relation [RESTRICTED], 1986 (Box 9 (7-Subject Files [RESTRICTED]), Folder 63)
  - Publications Received [RESTRICTED], 1972-1974; 2 folders (Box 9 (7-Subject Files [RESTRICTED]), Folder 64-65)
  - Quaker Committee on Social Rehabilitation, Inc. [RESTRICTED], 1970-1972 (Box 10 (7-Subject Files [RESTRICTED]), Folder 1)
  - Race and Community Relations Service [RESTRICTED], 1983 (Box 10 (7-Subject Files [RESTRICTED]), Folder 2)
  - Racial Disparities [RESTRICTED], 1985 (Box 10 (7-Subject Files [RESTRICTED]), Folder 3)
  - Recidivism [RESTRICTED], 1984 (Box 10 (7-Subject Files [RESTRICTED]), Folder 4)
  - Recidivism [RESTRICTED], 1985-1987 (Box 10 (7-Subject Files [RESTRICTED]), Folder 5)
  - Recommendations to the 1970 Legislature [RESTRICTED] (Box 10 (7-Subject Files [RESTRICTED]), Folder 6)
  - Recommendations to the 1971 Legislature [RESTRICTED] (Box 10 (7-Subject Files [RESTRICTED]), Folder 7)
  - Recommendations to the 1972 Legislature [RESTRICTED] (Box 10 (7-Subject Files [RESTRICTED]), Folder 8)
  - Recommendations to the 1975 Legislature [RESTRICTED] (Box 10 (7-Subject Files [RESTRICTED]), Folder 9)
  - Rehabilitation [RESTRICTED], 1968-1973 (Box 10 (7-Subject Files [RESTRICTED]), Folder 10)
  - Rehabilitation of the National Capital Area, Bureau of [RESTRICTED], 1972 (Box 10 (7-Subject Files [RESTRICTED]), Folder 11)
  - Release from Custody and Dismissal from Prosecution [RESTRICTED], 1971 (Box 10 (7-Subject Files [RESTRICTED]), Folder 12)
  - Report on Subject of Prison Reform [RESTRICTED], 1972 (Box 10 (7-Subject Files [RESTRICTED]), Folder 13)
  - Report of the Committee on Institutions and Offender Services on 1974-75 Visits to NYC Correctional Institutes [RESTRICTED], 1974-1975 (Box 10 (7-Subject Files [RESTRICTED]), Folder 14)
  - Report on "Victimless Crimes" in New York State [RESTRICTED], 1972 (Box 10 (7-Subject Files [RESTRICTED]), Folder 15)
  - "Rhetoric and Reality of Prison Reform" [RESTRICTED], 1972 (Box 10 (7-Subject Files [RESTRICTED]), Folder 16)
  - Rights of Prisoners [RESTRICTED], 1971 (Box 10 (7-Subject Files [RESTRICTED]), Folder 17)
  - Riker's Island, News Clippings [RESTRICTED], 1988 (Box 10 (7-Subject Files [RESTRICTED]), Folder 18)
  - Riker's Island - Problems, News Clippings [RESTRICTED], 1971-1976 (Box 10 (7-Subject Files [RESTRICTED]), Folder 19)
  - Riker's Island - Problems, News Clippings [RESTRICTED], 1976-1977 (Box 10 (7-Subject Files [RESTRICTED]), Folder 20)
  - Riker's Island Revolt, News Clippings [RESTRICTED], 1975 (Box 10 (7-Subject Files [RESTRICTED]), Folder 21)
  - Robinson to Driver to Easter (Study of Development of Involuntary Intoxication) [RESTRICTED], 1967 (Box 10 (7-Subject Files [RESTRICTED]), Folder 22)
  - Rochester Bureau of Municipal Research, Inc. [RESTRICTED], 1964 (Box 10 (7-Subject Files [RESTRICTED]), Folder 23)
  - Rochester Bureau of Municipal Research, Inc. [RESTRICTED], 1967-1972 (Box 10 (7-Subject Files [RESTRICTED]), Folder 24)
  - "Role of Race in the American Criminal Justice System" [RESTRICTED], 1982-1983 (Box 10 (7-Subject Files [RESTRICTED]), Folder 25)
  - Roosevelt Hospital Annual Report [RESTRICTED], 1974 (Box 10 (7-Subject Files [RESTRICTED]), Folder 26)
  - Rothman, David - Articles [RESTRICTED], 1973 (Box 10 (7-Subject Files [RESTRICTED]), Folder 27)
  - Roundtable Discussion on Criminal Sentencing [RESTRICTED], 1976-1977 (Box 10 (7-Subject Files [RESTRICTED]), Folder 28)
  - Runaway and Homeless Youth in New York City [RESTRICTED], 1984 (Box 10 (7-Subject Files [RESTRICTED]), Folder 29)
  - Saint Peter's Church [RESTRICTED], 1972 (Box 10 (7-Subject Files [RESTRICTED]), Folder 30)
  - Selective Incapacitation [RESTRICTED], 1982-1983; 2 folders (Box 10 (7-Subject Files [RESTRICTED]), Folder 31-32)
  - Selective Incapacitation [RESTRICTED], 1986 (Box 10 (7-Subject Files [RESTRICTED]), Folder 33)
  - Sentencing [RESTRICTED], 1977-1983 (Box 10 (7-Subject Files [RESTRICTED]), Folder 34)
  - Sentencing - Determinate [RESTRICTED], 1979-1984 (Box 10 (7-Subject Files [RESTRICTED]), Folder 35)
  - Sentencing Guidelines [RESTRICTED], 1982-1983 (Box 10 (7-Subject Files [RESTRICTED]), Folder 36)
  - Sentencing Guidelines [RESTRICTED], 1984-1986 (Box 10 (7-Subject Files [RESTRICTED]), Folder 37)
  - Sentencing Guidelines - U.S. Sentencing Commission [RESTRICTED], 1986 (Box 10 (7-Subject Files [RESTRICTED]), Folder 38)
  - Sentencing - Mandatory [RESTRICTED], 1977-1982 (Box 10 (7-Subject Files [RESTRICTED]), Folder 39)
  - Sentencing Policies [RESTRICTED], 1988 (Box 10 (7-Subject Files [RESTRICTED]), Folder 40)
  - Sentencing Practices, Procedures, and Consequences - Legal Aid Society Report [RESTRICTED], 1980 (Box 10 (7-Subject Files [RESTRICTED]), Folder 41)
  - Sentencing Reform [RESTRICTED], 1977 (Box 10 (7-Subject Files [RESTRICTED]), Folder 42)
  - Sexual Abuse, Crimes, Offenders, and Programs [RESTRICTED], 1986 (Box 10 (7-Subject Files [RESTRICTED]), Folder 43)
  - Sexual Issues [RESTRICTED], 1965-1972 (Box 10 (7-Subject Files [RESTRICTED]), Folder 44)
  - Short-term Adolescent Resident Training Center [RESTRICTED], 1962 (Box 10 (7-Subject Files [RESTRICTED]), Folder 45)
  - Short-term Detention - Official Reports [RESTRICTED], 1982-1983 (Box 10 (7-Subject Files [RESTRICTED]), Folder 46)
  - Should Alcoholics Be Absolved from Criminal Responsibility? [RESTRICTED], 1967 (Box 10 (7-Subject Files [RESTRICTED]), Folder 47)
  - Should Narcotics Be Prescribed to Addicts? No! [RESTRICTED], 1967 (Box 10 (7-Subject Files [RESTRICTED]), Folder 48)
  - Should the State Regulate Morality? [RESTRICTED], 1968 (Box 10 (7-Subject Files [RESTRICTED]), Folder 49)
  - Singer/Graflex Vocational Evaluation System [RESTRICTED], 1971-1972 (Box 10 (7-Subject Files [RESTRICTED]), Folder 50)
  - "Social Policy and the Future of Criminal Justice" [RESTRICTED], 1988 (Box 10 (7-Subject Files [RESTRICTED]), Folder 51)
  - Socio-economic Causes of Crime [RESTRICTED], 1986 (Box 10 (7-Subject Files [RESTRICTED]), Folder 52)
  - Some Observations on the Sociological Aspect of Narcotics Addiction [RESTRICTED], 1961 (Box 10 (7-Subject Files [RESTRICTED]), Folder 53)
  - South Forty Corporation [RESTRICTED], 1975 (Box 10 (7-Subject Files [RESTRICTED]), Folder 54)
  - Speakers' Bureau [RESTRICTED], 1986 (Box 10 (7-Subject Files [RESTRICTED]), Folder 55)
  - State Correctional Systems [RESTRICTED], 1961 (Box 10 (7-Subject Files [RESTRICTED]), Folder 56)
  - State of the Prisons - CANY Report [RESTRICTED], 1986 (Box 10 (7-Subject Files [RESTRICTED]), Folder 57)
  - State Prison Overcrowding: Parole and Good Time Proposals [RESTRICTED], 1983 (Box 10 (7-Subject Files [RESTRICTED]), Folder 58)
  - State Prison Overcrowding: Blue Ribbon Panel [RESTRICTED], 1983 (Box 10 (7-Subject Files [RESTRICTED]), Folder 59)
  - State Prison Overcrowding: Proposed Legislation [RESTRICTED], 1983-1984 (Box 10 (7-Subject Files [RESTRICTED]), Folder 60)
  - Stay'n Out [RESTRICTED], ca. 1980 (Box 10 (7-Subject Files [RESTRICTED]), Folder 61)
  - Strategy Memos to Board of Directors [RESTRICTED], 1987-1988 (Box 10 (7-Subject Files [RESTRICTED]), Folder 62)
  - Suicide in Prisons [RESTRICTED], 1969-1970 (Box 10 (7-Subject Files [RESTRICTED]), Folder 63)
  - Suicide Prevention: Officer's Handbook [RESTRICTED], 1986 (Box 10 (7-Subject Files [RESTRICTED]), Folder 64)
  - Survey of a Representative Sample of Addicts Prescribed Heroin [RESTRICTED], 1970 (Box 10 (7-Subject Files [RESTRICTED]), Folder 65)
  - Testimony for City Council on Bill No. 721 [RESTRICTED], 1968 (Box 10 (7-Subject Files [RESTRICTED]), Folder 66)
  - Texas [RESTRICTED], 1985-1987 (Box 10 (7-Subject Files [RESTRICTED]), Folder 67)
  - Therapeutic Abortions [RESTRICTED], 1967 (Box 10 (7-Subject Files [RESTRICTED]), Folder 68)
  - Toward a Crime Prevention Strategy [RESTRICTED], 1985 (Box 10 (7-Subject Files [RESTRICTED]), Folder 69)
  - Training Programs - General [RESTRICTED], 1966-1971 (Box 10 (7-Subject Files [RESTRICTED]), Folder 70)
  - Training Schools [RESTRICTED], 1970-1971 (Box 10 (7-Subject Files [RESTRICTED]), Folder 71)
  - Tri-State Consumers and Trade News [RESTRICTED], 1971 (Box 10 (7-Subject Files [RESTRICTED]), Folder 72)
  - U.N. Advisory Committee of NGO's to Social Defense [RESTRICTED], 1972-1973 (Box 11 (7-Subject Files [RESTRICTED]), Folder 1)
  - U.S. Department of Justice - Bureau of Prisons [RESTRICTED], 1960-1972 (Box 11 (7-Subject Files [RESTRICTED]), Folder 2)
  - U.S. Department of Justice - Crime [RESTRICTED], 1983-1984 (Box 11 (7-Subject Files [RESTRICTED]), Folder 3)
  - U.S. Department of Justice - Law Enforcement Assistance Administration [RESTRICTED], 1965-1978 (Box 11 (7-Subject Files [RESTRICTED]), Folder 4)
  - U.S. Supreme Court - Chronic Alcoholism and the 8th and 14th Amendments [RESTRICTED], 1965 (Box 11 (7-Subject Files [RESTRICTED]), Folder 5)
  - U.S. Supreme Court - Prison-related Cases [RESTRICTED], 1984 (Box 11 (7-Subject Files [RESTRICTED]), Folder 6)
  - Urban League News [RESTRICTED], 1971-1973 (Box 11 (7-Subject Files [RESTRICTED]), Folder 7)
  - Veatch Program [RESTRICTED], 1982-1985 (Box 11 (7-Subject Files [RESTRICTED]), Folder 8)
  - Vera Institute of Justice [RESTRICTED], 1986 (Box 11 (7-Subject Files [RESTRICTED]), Folder 9)
  - Vera Institute of Justice - Community Service [RESTRICTED], 1981-1985 (Box 11 (7-Subject Files [RESTRICTED]), Folder 10)
  - Vermont Department of Corrections - Newsletters [RESTRICTED], 1971-1973 (Box 11 (7-Subject Files [RESTRICTED]), Folder 11)
  - Vesey Street Letter [RESTRICTED], 1972-1976 (Box 11 (7-Subject Files [RESTRICTED]), Folder 12)
  - VISTA Riker's Island Project [RESTRICTED], ca. 1975 (Box 11 (7-Subject Files [RESTRICTED]), Folder 13)
  - Victim Compensation [RESTRICTED], 1965 (Box 11 (7-Subject Files [RESTRICTED]), Folder 14)
  - Victimless Crime [RESTRICTED], 1971-1972 (Box 11 (7-Subject Files [RESTRICTED]), Folder 15)
  - Victims of Crime [RESTRICTED], 1981-1982 (Box 11 (7-Subject Files [RESTRICTED]), Folder 16)
  - VISTO Report - "Summary of Movement and Activities of Volunteers and Probationers, April-June 1970" [RESTRICTED] (Box 11 (7-Subject Files [RESTRICTED]), Folder 17)
  - Vocational Foundation, Inc. [RESTRICTED], 1971 (Box 11 (7-Subject Files [RESTRICTED]), Folder 18)
  - Voluntary Correctional Service Agencies [RESTRICTED], Undated (Box 11 (7-Subject Files [RESTRICTED]), Folder 19)
  - Volunteers [RESTRICTED], 1971-1972 (Box 11 (7-Subject Files [RESTRICTED]), Folder 20)
  - Volunteers in Probation Conference, April 1972 [RESTRICTED], 1971-1972 (Box 11 (7-Subject Files [RESTRICTED]), Folder 21)
  - Von Hirsch, Andrew - Articles [RESTRICTED], 1979-1983 (Box 11 (7-Subject Files [RESTRICTED]), Folder 22)
  - Voters Against the Prison Construction Bond [RESTRICTED], 1981 (Box 11 (7-Subject Files [RESTRICTED]), Folder 23)
  - Westchester County, Action Plan to the Final Report of the Task Force on Corrections Overcrowding [RESTRICTED], 1987 (Box 11 (7-Subject Files [RESTRICTED]), Folder 24)
  - Westchester County Department of Community Mental Health, Annual Report [RESTRICTED], 1987 (Box 11 (7-Subject Files [RESTRICTED]), Folder 25)
  - Westchester County Department of Community Mental Health, Survey of Inpatient Care [RESTRICTED], 1983 (Box 11 (7-Subject Files [RESTRICTED]), Folder 26)
  - Westchester County - Directory of Community Mental Health Services [RESTRICTED], 1986 (Box 11 (7-Subject Files [RESTRICTED]), Folder 27)
  - Westchester County Task Force on Corrections Overcrowding, Final Report [RESTRICTED], 1987 (Box 11 (7-Subject Files [RESTRICTED]), Folder 28)
  - What Is Your Jail Like? [RESTRICTED], 1964 (Box 11 (7-Subject Files [RESTRICTED]), Folder 29)
  - What Prisons Do to People [RESTRICTED], 1985 (Box 11 (7-Subject Files [RESTRICTED]), Folder 30)
  - White Collar Crime [RESTRICTED], 1980-1985 (Box 11 (7-Subject Files [RESTRICTED]), Folder 31)
  - Women in Jail [RESTRICTED], 1982 (Box 11 (7-Subject Files [RESTRICTED]), Folder 32)
  - "Women in Prison: Inequitable Treatment Requires Action" [RESTRICTED], 1980 (Box 11 (7-Subject Files [RESTRICTED]), Folder 33)
  - Women's Prison Association and Hopper Home [RESTRICTED], 1974-1977 (Box 11 (7-Subject Files [RESTRICTED]), Folder 34)
  - Work Camps for Youth in Trouble [RESTRICTED], 1960s (Box 11 (7-Subject Files [RESTRICTED]), Folder 35)
  - Work Release vs. Prison Construction [RESTRICTED], 1988 (Box 11 (7-Subject Files [RESTRICTED]), Folder 36)
  - Work Release Programs for Prisoners [RESTRICTED], 1966-1968 (Box 11 (7-Subject Files [RESTRICTED]), Folder 37)
  - Would You Hire an Ex-Convict [RESTRICTED], 1972 (Box 11 (7-Subject Files [RESTRICTED]), Folder 38)
  - Wyoming Correctional Facility [RESTRICTED], 1985 (Box 11 (7-Subject Files [RESTRICTED]), Folder 39)
  - Youth Crime: New York's Two Varieties [RESTRICTED], 1983 (Box 11 (7-Subject Files [RESTRICTED]), Folder 40)
  - Youth Study [RESTRICTED], 1961 (Box 11 (7-Subject Files [RESTRICTED]), Folder 41)
  - You've Come a Long Way, Baby (Saloons) [RESTRICTED], 1969 (Box 11 (7-Subject Files [RESTRICTED]), Folder 42)
- Miscellaneous Publication Files, 1944; 1976-1979; 1982-1986; 8; 0.33 cubic ft.
  This series consists of material produced or collected by the Correctional Association. It contains a handbook, manual, brochure, book, pamphlet, bulletins, annual reports, and bulletins published by the Correctional Association, and published and unpublished material that the Association gathered and reproduced upon request. Topics covered include alcoholism, the prison population explosion, correctional costs, and annual reports of the Association to the New York State Legislature. Only one publication dates from 1944.
  - Alcohol and Alcoholism: A Police Handbook, 1978 (Box 1 (8-Miscellaneous Publication Files), Folder 1)
  - Calculating Criminal Justice Costs: A Manual for Citizens, 1979 (Box 1 (8-Miscellaneous Publication Files), Folder 2)